<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Explore Life</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2008-03-11://1</id>
    <updated>2010-07-13T10:21:42Z</updated>
    
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type Personal 4.1</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Dust on My Shoes</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/06/dust-on-my-shoes.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.32</id>

    <published>2010-06-28T09:19:58Z</published>
    <updated>2010-07-13T10:21:42Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[Peter Pinney's first book Dust on My Shoes is an account of an overland journey which he made between 1948 - 1950 from Greece to Burma via Turkey, Syria, Lebanon, Iraq, Iran, Afghanistan, Pakistan &amp; India.&nbsp; It is now known to Westerners as the Overland Route or Dope Trail. "I am just travelling. Some people like to grow crops, others to make music, or sit in small shops, like your father, selling pots. I am unsuccessful in all the things which I enjoy most, except the one thing which I find best of all: and that is travelling. To pass...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Traveller" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="peterpinney" label="peter pinney" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Peter Pinney's first book <em>Dust on My Shoes</em> is an account of an overland journey which he made between 1948 - 1950 from Greece to Burma via Turkey, Syria, Lebanon, Iraq, Iran, Afghanistan, Pakistan &amp; India.&nbsp; It is now known to Westerners as the Overland Route or Dope Trail.</p>
<p>"I am just travelling. Some people like to grow crops, others to make music, or sit in small shops, like your father, selling pots. I am unsuccessful in all the things which I enjoy most, except the one thing which I find best of all: and that is travelling. To pass through a new country is something very dear to my heart."&nbsp; an excerpt from <em>Dust on My Shoes - Peter Pinney. </em></p>
<p>
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image"><img style="MARGIN: 0px 0px 20px 20px; FLOAT: right" class="mt-image-right" alt="PP.jpg" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/PP.jpg" width="83" height="94" /></span>Love it! Love it!&nbsp; When I first read this paragraph, I had just plunged in for a warm soak in the tub and had this great book for company.&nbsp; By the time I considered putting the book down, I was frozen, since the water had gone cold and the candlelight had faded away to a dim sliver, and I could no longer see!&nbsp; His words just reached inside my heart &amp; snatched out the adventure that I so longed for.&nbsp; I couldn't get enough of his adventurous &amp; wild&nbsp;encounters on what was&nbsp;at times,&nbsp;a very terrifying journey.&nbsp; I really just wanted to walk in his shoes.&nbsp; </p>
<p>Have you ever felt that yearning for adventure where you simply want to <em>scream out loud, as loud as you can! Get me the hell out of&nbsp;here!!!!&nbsp; </em>Where the everyday joys of life with money &amp; security, well, just doesn't do it for you?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Our conditioning from society means that our first impression of riches are material items like cars, homes, money &amp; fashion.&nbsp; I am here to tell you along with Peter Pinney [professional traveler, then writer] that nothing moves me quite like a smile from a person,&nbsp;dressed in rags for clothes, most teeth missing, weathered faces &amp; beings which wreak from needing a good shower.&nbsp;&nbsp;Nothing else&nbsp;matters when we engage our hearts&nbsp;through a smile and try to converse with our hands, since we cannot understand each other!&nbsp; When you constantly throw yourself into experiences like this, it is so damn hard to just settle for less.&nbsp; AND I mean the day to day slog in western society with all our grandeur is&nbsp;<em>less</em> than the riches I gain from a fleeting conversation, a smile or embrace I receive from one country to the next. </p>
<p>I'm not someone who&nbsp;"has&nbsp;money", as such&nbsp;[although, even in my position I&nbsp;would be better off than many]. I feel&nbsp;blessed that I've gained so many amazing exchanges in my life,&nbsp;that this is my wealth.&nbsp; I would have to say, that I am most content &amp; fulfilled when I am travelling.&nbsp; An abundance of more worldliness and wisdom is all I cherish.</p>
<p>I live to travel.&nbsp; It is truly the greatest educator of life!&nbsp; Try topping up&nbsp;your life&nbsp;until it overflows with soulful experiences.&nbsp;When everything around you is cold, the reminiscences will warm you.</p>
<p>Peter Pinney &amp; his wife Estelle settled in&nbsp;Brisbane in the 1980's. He passed away in 1992. Noted here is the website <a href="www.dustonmyshoes.com">Dust on My Shoes </a>however there are a great deal more explorations of his life worth discovering.&nbsp;He is a legend in my eyes.&nbsp; I only wish I had the fortune of meeting with him. </p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Lake Eyre</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/06/lake-eyre.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.31</id>

    <published>2010-06-24T07:40:25Z</published>
    <updated>2010-06-28T10:33:48Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[Did you know Lake Eyre has a yacht club?&nbsp; Lake Eyre has been bone dry for numerous years until more recent times.&nbsp; This year it is at it's fullest in 20 years.&nbsp; Yachties are excited in the lead up to their participation in the Lake Eyre Yacht Club Regatta 05-09 Jul 2010. How about that?&nbsp; Off to the desert with yacht &amp; trailer in tow!&nbsp;A site to be seen as yachties converge on the South Australian Outback&nbsp;where the lake meets dramatic desert landscapes! If you don't have a trailer sailer, do not fret!&nbsp; Access&nbsp;Lake Eyre by scenic flight from Coober...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Australia" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="lakeeyreyachtclubgreatsouthernrail" label="Lake Eyre Yacht Club Great Southern Rail" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Did you know Lake Eyre has a yacht club?&nbsp; Lake Eyre has been bone dry for numerous years until more recent times.&nbsp; This year it is at it's fullest in 20 years.&nbsp; Yachties are excited in the lead up to their participation in the Lake Eyre Yacht Club Regatta 05-09 Jul 2010.</p>
<p>How about that?&nbsp; Off to the desert with yacht &amp; trailer in tow!&nbsp;A site to be seen as yachties converge on the South Australian Outback&nbsp;where the lake meets dramatic desert landscapes!</p>
<p>If you don't have a trailer sailer, do not fret!&nbsp; Access&nbsp;Lake Eyre by scenic flight from Coober Pedy and fly the length and breadth of this natural wonder.&nbsp; Experience the luxury of rail travel on the spectacular Ghan whilst observing the amazing outback of the Northern Territory from Darwin to Manguri via Katherine and Alice Springs.&nbsp; Certainly, for the lucky few! Now's the time to get onboard and encounter the magnificent native bush of Australia!&nbsp; <a href="http://www.gsr.com.au/site/the_ghan/packages/a_natural_wonder.jsp">Click for packages..</a></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Invest in Romance</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/05/invest-in-romance-tsax.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.30</id>

    <published>2010-05-11T02:16:43Z</published>
    <updated>2010-05-11T03:09:40Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[The RECHARGE packages focus on exactly that, recharging relationships wi thout leaving a hole in the pocket. 6 night getaways start from $413 per couple. RENEW is about taking time out to discover and rediscover oneself and the loved one in an unforgettably unique getaway. 6 night getaways start from $1259 per couple. And REKINDLE is for those that can not put a price tag on their relationship and want to truly spoil each other with a getaway of a lifetime. Packages start from $2868 per couple. To&nbsp;receive&nbsp;copy of the extensive e-brochure simply contact us at EXPLORE LIFE a proud...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Newsletter info" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<p>The <span style="COLOR: #ff0000"><strong>RECHARGE</strong></span><span style="COLOR: #000000"><strong> </strong></span>packages focus on exactly that, <strong><em>recharging relationships wi thout leaving a hole in the pocket</em></strong>. 6 night getaways start from $413 per couple.</p>
<p><strong><span style="COLOR: #ff0000">RENEW </span></strong>is about <strong><em>taking time out to discover and rediscover oneself and the loved one in an unforgettably unique getaway</em></strong>. 6 night getaways start from $1259 per couple.</p>
<p>And <span style="COLOR: #ff0000"><strong>REKINDLE</strong></span> is <strong><em>for those that can not put a price tag on their relationship and want to truly spoil each other with a getaway of a lifetime</em></strong>. Packages start from $2868 per couple.</p>
<p>
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image"><img style="MARGIN: 0px 20px 20px 0px; WIDTH: 474px; FLOAT: left; HEIGHT: 391px" class="mt-image-left" alt="" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/Blossoms%205737B.JPG" width="640" height="427" /></span>To&nbsp;receive&nbsp;copy of the extensive e-brochure simply contact us at <span style="COLOR: #ff0000"><strong>EXPLORE LIFE </strong></span><strong>a proud affiliate of Travelscene American Express</strong> 
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Viwa Island</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/05/viwa-island.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.29</id>

    <published>2010-05-11T01:58:17Z</published>
    <updated>2010-06-29T07:05:02Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[TAKE ME THERE!!!!!!!&nbsp; Well, I've been actually, but have you? Viwa Island Resort,&nbsp;is pure paradise!&nbsp;Located in the Yasawa Islands Fiji, it is one of those places that you'll be just&nbsp;itchin'&nbsp;to exchange&nbsp;those three little words!&nbsp; Wonderful Wooden thatched roof,&nbsp;Fijian Bures [total 11] are dotted spaciously along the white sandy beachfront.&nbsp; I enjoyed my own space alone&nbsp;[I love you...VIWA!]&nbsp;and stayed in Bure # 6 which had magical views of the inviting deep blue sea, as&nbsp;all the bures do.&nbsp; I really felt like I had the island to myself [I practically did!].&nbsp; Multitudes of attentive&nbsp;staff&nbsp;reached out to assist my every whim,&nbsp;always with their...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="South Pacific" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="viwaisland" label="Viwa Island" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<p><font color="#000000"><strong><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt">TAKE ME THERE!!!!!!!&nbsp; </span></strong><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt">Well, I've been actually, but have you?</span></em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><o:p></o:p></span></font></p>
<p><strong><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">Viwa Island Resort,&nbsp;is pure paradise!&nbsp;</font></span></strong><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">Located in the Yasawa Islands Fiji, it is one of those places that you'll be just&nbsp;itchin'&nbsp;to exchange&nbsp;</font><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: red">those three little words!</span></em><span style="COLOR: red">&nbsp;</span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">Wonderful Wooden thatched roof,&nbsp;Fijian Bures [total 11] are dotted spaciously along the white sandy beachfront.&nbsp; I enjoyed my own space alone&nbsp;[</font><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: red">I love you...</span></em><font color="#000000"><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">VIWA!]</span></em>&nbsp;and stayed in Bure # 6 which had magical views of the inviting deep blue sea, as&nbsp;all the bures do.&nbsp; I really felt like I had the island to myself [<em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">I practically did!]</span></em>.&nbsp; Multitudes of attentive&nbsp;staff&nbsp;reached out to assist my every whim,&nbsp;always with their broad Fijian smiles and warm natured hearts.&nbsp;<o:p></o:p></font></span></p>
<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">Charlie and his fire lighting, Seko&nbsp;seranading guests with his singing trio, Mereani and her magical massages, Michelle, Des, Alf &amp; family [owner/managers] ensuring your every need is fulfilled. I could go on and on about the staff and single handedly name all kinds of individuals from the garden keepers to the receptionists to the chef's but I will fill the page and you would learn nothing else!&nbsp; So you get the picture.&nbsp;&nbsp;The staff of <st1:PlaceName w:st="on">Viwa</st1:PlaceName> <st1:PlaceType w:st="on">Island</st1:PlaceType> are it's&nbsp;best asset [hard call] but people &amp; their passion for service can really make or break your love affair with <st1:place w:st="on"><st1:country-region w:st="on">Fiji</st1:country-region></st1:place>.&nbsp;<o:p></o:p></font></span></p>
<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">It is a credit to the&nbsp;Downing Family to consistently produce a 4 star unspoilt haven,&nbsp;with 5 star <em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">soul.</span></em>&nbsp;&nbsp;I dropped a few tears in the ocean as I hugged, kissed and waved everybody goodbye.&nbsp; Happy times were had, that is for sure.<o:p></o:p></font></span></p>
<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image"><img style="WIDTH: 523px; HEIGHT: 480px" class="mt-image-none" alt="Viwa Island Moet 087B.jpg" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/Viwa%20Island%20Moet%20087B.jpg" width="640" height="480" /></span>I truly couldn't get enough of this place. I wanted to join the management team and stay! It's natural surrounds will take your breath away. For at least an entire hour, I lay at the waters edge to feel cleansed by the soft rolling surf as it ebbed and waned.<em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial"> I giggled like a little girl, </span></em>as my legs got flung high above my shoulders and twisted my body into oblivion. It was so peaceful, so comfortable, so damn loveable, that many more hours could of passed by me without a care in the world.&nbsp; <o:p></o:p></font></span></p>
<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt"><font color="#000000">From just a few metres away, I heard the mellow tones from my bure. The sweet sound of ice clanging, a&nbsp;cork popping and bubbles of my <em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">duty free Moet</span></em> being poured, stole me away from my sandy beach bliss.&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">Life is such a beach!</span></strong></font><o:p></o:p></span></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Boorman Eco</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/05/romance-me.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.28</id>

    <published>2010-05-07T06:18:55Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-23T01:39:28Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[ ROMANCE ME!&nbsp; &nbsp; Fill your lungs with the crisp, clean mountain air and smell the freshness.&nbsp; The sight of the canopy at first light is enchanting. To wake to the music of the forest is pure pleasure.&nbsp; Feel the dew from the grass under your feet and the cool air kissing your skin.&nbsp; &nbsp; Sounds like the perfect retreat for a couple, yes?&nbsp; Slight hitch!&nbsp; We just broke up.&nbsp; Ironically, this was my birthday gift for him!&nbsp; So off on a romantic weekend for two I trot with my beautiful blue heeler, Lucy!&nbsp; Everyone has to have their hearts...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Australia" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Australia" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="boormaneco" label="Boorman Eco" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana" lang="EN-AU"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"><b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"><u></u></b><o:p> 
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">ROMANCE ME!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p></u2:p>&nbsp;<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Fill your lungs with the crisp, clean mountain air and smell the freshness.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The sight of the canopy at first light is enchanting. To wake to the music of the forest is pure pleasure.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Feel the dew from the grass under your feet and the cool air kissing your skin.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><span style="mso-spacerun: yes"></span></span>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><span style="mso-spacerun: yes">Sounds like the perfect retreat for a couple, yes?&nbsp; Slight hitch!&nbsp; We just broke up.&nbsp; Ironically, this was my birthday gift for him!&nbsp; So off on a romantic weekend for two I trot with my beautiful blue heeler, Lucy!&nbsp; Everyone has to have their hearts broken once though, right?&nbsp; It's how the light gets in.&nbsp; The cracks shape us, make us who we are.&nbsp; I just needed to go nurse mine for a bit!&nbsp;&nbsp;Tucked away in Maleny's Hinterland you'll find her.....and j</span>ust having the taste&nbsp;for a short while, left me salivating for more. <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">It engages all your senses!&nbsp; It's my special place.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>On driving down the steep private road for the very first time, I slammed the brakes on <i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal">[poor Lucy - my blue heeler - tumbled from the back seat!]</i>. I stopped to admire what stood in front of my eyes.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>This silver [corrugated iron] majestic feature was shining, as the afternoon sun lit her up in the spotlight.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Her beauty commanded presence as she stood upon the rock face, surrounded by dense rainforest which draped dramatically into the valley below.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Her name:<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span><b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal"><u><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 11pt; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-ansi-language: EN-AU; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA" lang="EN-AU">Boorman Eco</span><u2:p></u2:p></u></b></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"></o:p></font></font></span>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana" lang="EN-AU"><o:p><font color="#000000" size="3">
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image">&nbsp;</span>
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image"><img style="MARGIN: 0px 0px 20px 20px; WIDTH: 493px; FLOAT: right; HEIGHT: 394px" class="mt-image-right" alt="Boorman Eco 030B.jpg" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/Boorman%20Eco%20030B.jpg" width="640" height="480" /></span>&nbsp;</font></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana" lang="EN-AU"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"></font></font></span>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Verdana" lang="EN-AU"><font size="3"><font color="#000000">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; </p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">An elegant black piano greets me,&nbsp;is staring at me, begging me to play to compliment the sounds of the wilderness.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I oblige but can't do it justice, since as a child I had only learnt the organ.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Each day however it grabs my attention and I play a few keys as if I am a star from the movie SHINE [<em>Geoffrey Rush</em>].</span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">"Oh!" The fireplace I exclaim!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p></u2:p>&nbsp;<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Robyn who is introducing me to Boorman Eco [<em>Robyn &amp; Greg are the local caretakers</em>] comments, "You won't need one at this time of year though, would you?" <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">&nbsp;<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">I reply, "Probably not, but every inch of me wants to always indulge and partake fully in the experience and opportunities, so to have a fire would be extremely fulfilling!". <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">[Can't say my childhood growing up in the bush taught me how to light one!]</span></em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>We were most often trying to put fires out that got away to the next cane paddock and wreaked havoc!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>My persistence got me a fire after my fourth attempt.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I finally felt more content.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Thereafter I indulged in a fire every night for my 4 night stay and am proud to say I could light one without firelighters!</span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Bubble bath and my Dermalogica Stress Relief oil along with Philip's cellar red <em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">[generously provided by the Boorman's]</span></em> were vital to my longing bath experience.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The bathtub was humongous!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I could lie down the length of it and I only filled it a quarter full to be covered!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>It was sooooo deep!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>From my tub was an awe-inspiring view out to the wilderness.</span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">I opened up every door and window, every louvre, and kept it that way day &amp; night during my entire stay.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>It was like 6 star sophisticated camping amongst the vines, except better, since I could admire not only the openness of the structure but the building itself.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Most people want mirrors on the ceilings of their bedrooms.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I was ecstatic to gratify in the wooden roof.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The hardwood design was throughout upper &amp; lower portions of the house but also in the garage!</span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Wood!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Wood! <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span><st1:City w:st="on"><st1:place w:st="on"><u3:City u4:st="on"><u3:place u4:st="on">Woodland</st1:place></st1:City></u3:place></u3:City>! <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Wood was everywhere and it blended perfectly with the corrugated iron externally.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Every wall that could be bi-folded by windows or doors was! <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">And it wasn't just in the walls. <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span><st1:City w:st="on"><st1:place w:st="on"><u3:City u4:st="on"><u3:place u4:st="on">Woodland</st1:place></st1:City></u3:place></u3:City> was far and wide, high and low!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Ample opportunities presented themselves to trek the mountains through fairly open canopy and a surprisingly wet environment, even though the sun filters through the tree line. The Boorman's have done an amazing job on conserving the bushland which is continually ongoing of course.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>On their plantation, they have their own private access walks&nbsp;which I discovered and loved the most.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>There is also access to one of the GREAT WALKS from their private road entrance.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I did that too and met some equally joyous walker's enroute. </span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">A simple but ultra comfortable, amazingly designed home, contrasts with elegance, sophistication and luxury.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The added benefit of the private hinterland beckoning at your doorstep just makes the entire experience divine!</span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><u2:p>&nbsp;</u2:p></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">What's missing??<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;&nbsp; </span>Can someone <em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">please</span></em> bring me breakfast in bed?<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;&nbsp; </span><em><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial">[Ah...<st1:City w:st="on"><st1:place w:st="on"><u3:place u4:st="on"><u3:City u4:st="on">Butler</st1:place></st1:City></u3:City></u3:place> service!]</span></em><span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;&nbsp; </span>....Or perhaps a new beau???? </span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: #333333; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p></o:p></span></p><u2:p></u2:p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p>&nbsp;</o:p></span></p></font></font></span>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Solomon Islands</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2010/02/nature-lovers-paradise.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2010://1.23</id>

    <published>2010-02-11T04:12:25Z</published>
    <updated>2010-09-23T03:51:12Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[ OMG (oh my god!)... on landing in Honiara I thought... "S**t what sort of hell hole have I booked myself into!&nbsp; Overwhelmingly humid &amp; hot, with sweat dripping off me, I disobligingly stand in line to complete custom formalities, only to be told by those ahead of me "photocopy no good" and the scurry of people filing backwards to get new original forms, unlike we were handed on the aircraft. By the time I work out what's going on, I find myself at the very end of the line. Additionally, I,&nbsp;am the last person to clear customs and therefore,...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="South Pacific" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="South Pacific" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="woodenbungalowsfishinglolaislanduepiresortmaravolagoonsanbisresort" label="wooden bungalows fishing Lola island Uepi resort maravo Lagoon Sanbis resort" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<span lang="EN-AU"><font color="#000000" size="3"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"> 
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image"><img style="MARGIN: 0px 0px 20px 20px; FLOAT: right" class="mt-image-right" alt="Solomons snorkel.JPG" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/Solomons%20snorkel.JPG" width="240" height="180" /></span>OMG (oh my god!)...<strong> </strong>on landing in Honiara I thought... "S**t what sort of hell hole have I booked myself into!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Overwhelmingly humid &amp; hot, with sweat dripping off me, I disobligingly stand in line to complete custom formalities, only to be told by those ahead of me "photocopy no good" and the scurry of people filing backwards to get new original forms, unlike we were handed on the aircraft. By the time I work out what's going on, I find myself at the very end of the line. Additionally, I,&nbsp;am the last person to clear customs and therefore, also the last hope of a fare for the multitude of taxi driver's patiently waiting in the arrival halls!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>"Taxi? You want Taxi?" <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span>With fishing rods and duffle bag a hoist and patience running very thin, I struggle to walk half a kilometre along a dirt road to the hardly distinguishable, domestic terminal -&nbsp;a tin roof shed! &nbsp;<o:p></o:p></span> 
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p>&nbsp;</o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Alas!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Times are a changing as our low flying aircraft provides me with some WOW experiences.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The cold red cordial went down a treat and in childlike fashion I throw myself out of my seat from one side of the aircraft to the next to view the magical and pristine lagoons below me.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Excitement builds as I imagine drenching myself in the turquoise blue water with the colourful, abundant marine life swimming around me.<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p>&nbsp;</o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Black tip reef sharks, Lion fish, Nemos, grey nurse sharks, giant clams, zebra sea snakes, dolphins, swarms of reef fish, dart fish, pretty coral, Fish! Fish! Fish! And this is simply just snorkelling!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Uepi Island resort on the Maravo Lagoon is in such a wonderful location, is well established and offers quality timber bungalows on the beach.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Each are scattered comfortably away from each other over the grounds of the resort. The owners, the Kelly family Jill, Grant, Wes &amp; Jason originally from North Queensland have been long established and really know the Solomon's way of life. They live and breathe the heart and soul of the Solomon people and share this with their guests at the resort.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Uepi is amazing for both diving and snorkelling and the food is yummy!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Swimming &amp; eyeballing more than 25 sharks in the shallows was such an exhilarating experience!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I just couldn't get enough of it!<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"></span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"></span>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image">&nbsp;</span>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><img style="MARGIN: 0px 20px 20px 0px; FLOAT: left" class="mt-image-left" alt="Fishing Sol's.jpg" src="http://www.explorelife.com.au/Fishing%20Sol%27s.jpg" width="328" height="480" />Jo and Lisa from Zipolo Habu otherwise referred to as "Lola" on beautiful Lola Island provide a range of accommodation from traditional to deluxe bungalows.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I stayed in the traditional huts with shared bathroom facilities. All have lovely views of the ocean in front of you and although, a little hot when the generator goes off at 11pm, the mosquito nets, fridge &amp; gas cooker were added comforts.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Crayfish for dinner every night - who could complain!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>It's a top spot for fishing and we joined another keen angler on a charter who gave us invaluable tips on popping &amp; bottom fishing.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I must say, I did beat the men in the fishing competition with the MOST, the LARGEST &amp; the&nbsp;BEST QUALITY fish of the day!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>YAY!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>GO GIRL!</p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal">&nbsp;</p></span>
<p></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; COLOR: black; FONT-SIZE: 9pt; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-ansi-language: EN-AU; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA" lang="EN-AU">I waved goodbye to Lola as I jumped aboard a tinny for a 30minute ride to <st1:place w:st="on"><st1:PlaceName w:st="on">Munda</st1:PlaceName> <st1:PlaceType w:st="on">Airport</st1:PlaceType></st1:place>.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The flight from Munda to Gizo is only 15minutes.&nbsp; Before long, I found myself being whisked away on a boat from Gizo airport,&nbsp;to Sanbis Resort.</span><span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Spectacular!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>What a top spot.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>High quality wooden bungalows intricately dotted along the waters edge immediately grabbed my attention. The white sandy beach, bungalow overlooking the beautiful reef lagoon, along with the manicured natural grounds&nbsp;&amp; resort facilities makes for a very enjoyable stay. 'Hans' a passionate gentleman with Swiss origin, owns and manages Sanbis along with his well trained local Sol team.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The European influence is highly exposed in the quality of the workmanship, layout structure, interiors and design. Conversations with staff were a pleasure and meals, beverages and the coffee a delight!<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Access to some surf breaks and fishing spots were very joyous experiences, thankfully to the generosity provided by Doug &amp; Karen whom were guests staying at Sanbis. They had&nbsp;arrived with their own boat.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The personal and intimate nature of Sanbis, allows great privacy, yet ample opportunity to befriend other guests.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I love building relationships with new people and I found so much joy in discovering &amp; sharing the interests and lives of those around us.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>I guess that this is the ultimate reward that I felt gifted with, from staying at Sanbis resort.<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p>&nbsp;</o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">Solomon Islands... or Sol's as I prefer to refer to them are raw and adventurous.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>The basic tourism infrastructure can at times be frustrating but the beauty you consistently find yourself amongst, will take your breath away.<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU"><o:p>
<span style="DISPLAY: inline" class="mt-enclosure mt-enclosure-image">&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</o:p></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Arial', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 9pt" lang="EN-AU">BYO: ice, air-conditioning, &amp; boat or leave such comforts at home and enjoy the hospitality and excitement that an encounter in the Solomon Islands will provide.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p style="MARGIN: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"></font></span>&nbsp;</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Explore Life</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2008/05/share-our-passion.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2008://1.21</id>

    <published>2008-05-27T06:28:32Z</published>
    <updated>2010-06-28T00:03:09Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[share our passion feel the adventure explore our world &nbsp; Is your life full of riches or rich experiences?&nbsp; Live your life fully...right to the top! &nbsp;...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Traveller" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="richexperiencesbeatravellernotatouristlivetotravel" label="rich experiences be a traveller not a tourist live to travel" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[<p><strong>share</strong> our passion</p>
<p><strong>feel</strong> the adventure</p>
<p><strong>explore</strong> our world</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Is your life full of riches or rich experiences?&nbsp; Live your life fully...right to the top!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Antarctica</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2008/05/explore-our-world.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,2006://1.19</id>

    <published>2008-05-26T07:02:41Z</published>
    <updated>2010-06-29T07:06:12Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[Imagine yourself in a peaceful wilderness, surrounded by a mass of bluish-green sea, silently drifting in the sunshine surrounded by a landscape so awe-inspiringly beautiful, immaculately untouched ice cliffs staring down at you from above. In comparison, the zodiac your sitting mesmerised in, feels like the size of a matchbox in this vast expanse of ocean and floating ice.&nbsp; Suddenly, a BANG!&nbsp; A thunderous explosion of violet-crumble like ice, peels off the mountainside and crashes into the polar sea!&nbsp; Well, don't just imagine it - get out there!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Antarctica, 2006...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Antarctica" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Antarctica" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    <category term="adventureantarctica" label="Adventure antarctica" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[Imagine yourself in a peaceful wilderness, surrounded by a mass of bluish-green sea, silently drifting in the sunshine surrounded by a landscape so awe-inspiringly beautiful, immaculately untouched ice cliffs staring down at you from above. In comparison, the zodiac your sitting mesmerised in, feels like the size of a matchbox in this vast expanse of ocean and floating ice.<span>&nbsp; </span>Suddenly, a BANG!<span>&nbsp; </span>A thunderous explosion of violet-crumble like ice, peels off the mountainside and crashes into the polar sea!<span>&nbsp; </span><o:p></o:p>
<p>Well, don't just imagine it - get out there!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><b>Antarctica, 2006</b><br /><br /></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Zimbabwe</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.explorelife.com.au/2008/05/feel-the-adventure.html" />
    <id>tag:www.explorelife.com.au,1991://1.18</id>

    <published>2008-05-26T07:02:07Z</published>
    <updated>2010-06-29T07:06:51Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[I was standing, straddled across the back of an open-air jeep, with my head down. My film had just ran out, when the guide said to me "Don't move. Breathe, but just don't move".&nbsp; There before me, only 2 metres away was a lone lion.&nbsp; His eyes were so focused on mine. It was like watching a bullet travel in slow motion towards its target. A detour was out of the question.&nbsp; I gasped for breath.&nbsp; His mane resembled a caramel coloured, 'eighties', over-teased afro.&nbsp; Confident of his own masculinity, he started to circle the jeep.&nbsp; As each muscle contracted...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name>Chrissy Lando</name>
        <uri>http://www.explorelife.com.au</uri>
    </author>
    
        <category term="Africa" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Chrissy&apos;s Blog" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
        <category term="Exquisite Experiences!" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category" />
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://www.explorelife.com.au/">
        <![CDATA[I was standing, straddled across the back of an open-air jeep, with my head down. My film had just ran out, when the guide said to me "Don't move. Breathe, but just don't move".<span>&nbsp; </span>There before me, only 2 metres away was a lone lion.<span>&nbsp; </span>His eyes were so focused on mine. It was like watching a bullet travel in slow motion towards its target. A detour was out of the question.<span>&nbsp; </span>I gasped for breath.<span>&nbsp; </span>His mane resembled a caramel coloured, 'eighties', over-teased afro.<span>&nbsp; </span>Confident of his own masculinity, he started to circle the jeep.<span>&nbsp; </span>As each muscle contracted with every step, I observed an abnormally high definition of detail protruding visibly through his skin.<span>&nbsp; </span>My heart was beating so damn hard and loud that I thought I was being ambushed by native warriors.<span>&nbsp; </span>Although spellbound, it wasn't long before I snapped into consciousness.<span>&nbsp; </span>My mind quickly focused as I realised my only concern was the majestic lion in front of me! <br /><br /><b>Zimbabwe 1991</b> &nbsp; ]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
